Ernest Joseph King Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Miscellany, 1909-1966 (Box 37-39)
  - Design for Pye-King range machine, 1909
  - Envelopes
  - General
  - Inventory of and receipt for furniture, 1925
  - Map of Southeast Asia, 1944
  - Memorabilia, 1937-1945
  - Newspaper clippings, 1923-1949
  - Photograph and cartoon of King
  - Photographs, United States Naval Air Station, Seattle, Wash., 1938-1938
  - Special passport, 1917
- 2023 Addition, 1947-1991 (Box 39)
  Newsletter article and speech.
  Arranged alphabetically by material type.
  - Newsletter article, "Admiral King talks about Allied Strategy, July 1943," 1991 (Box 39)
  - Speech, "Some Aspects of the High Command in World War II," 1947 (Box 39)